https://www.mirajewelry.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
NecklacesEarringsSterling Silver OverlayBraceletsCharmsPinsBest SellersAccessoriesWine Country JewelryGrape PendantsGrape EarringsGrape BraceletsGrape CharmsGrape PinsBest SellersAccessories
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Personal Information
MIRA Jewelry is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. We do not share personal information provided by site visitors with any third party. In particular, we do not rent, loan or sell mailing lists of site visitors to anyone.
MIRA Jewelry does not send unsolicited emails or spam of any type.
In order to process your order, MIRAJewelry.com must obtain some information from each customer. Examples of information you may provide us with include: name, postal address, e-mail address & phone number which will be used to process your order. Your information is kept safe, secure and private and will not be used for anything other then getting you your order.
Cookies
MIRAJewelry.com uses the feature of your internet web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. MIRAJewelry.com uses these cookie files to track your clicks as you go through the MIRA Jewelry web site. We use these cookies to keep track of what parts of our web site attract the most traffic and to determine how to make our web site easier to navigate. These cookies cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.
MIRAJewelry.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you.
Packaging Privacy
All items purchased from MIRAJewelry.com are shipped in USPS Priority Mail packaging or a plain cardboard box. The return address name on our packages is: MIRA.
Credit Card Security & Safe Shopping
MIRAJewelry.com is a highly secure website and all payments are processed securely using 256-bit or higher Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption. Our customers information is protected and they can enjoy safe shopping.
Copyright
© 1998 - 2020 MIRA Jewelry. All Rights Reserved.
MIRA® is a Federally Registered Trademark
